Guide to the Penn State Extension records 01131
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- 01: County Reports, 1
  - Philadelphia County
    - Philly Project, 2008; cuid1251 (Box 238)
    - Project, 2000-2002; cuid1257 (Box 239)
    - Resource Center, 2002-2004; cuid1272 (Box 239)
    - SE CED Leadership Team Meeting - Adobe Connect, 2011; cuid1273 (Box 240)
    - Silver Award, cuid1213; 1 Items; Artifacts--Material Objects--Medals (Box 199)
    - Soils of Pennsylvania - Progress Report #365, 1977/11; cuid1214; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Staff Positions, 1998-2004; cuid1261 (Box 239)
    - Strategic Planning Information, 1992/03; cuid1215; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Tips on Energy Saving for Home Gardener, cuid1216; 1 Items (Box 200)
    - To Make the Best Better, 4-H Clubs Scatter Site III, undated; cuid1217; 1 Items; Artifacts--Textiles--Banners (Box 201)
    - Urban Gardening, cuid1218; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening - Harvest Show Outstanding Exhibit - certificate of merit, 1997; cuid1219; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening - Inservice Training Program, cuid1220; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program, cuid1221; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Color (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program, cuid1222; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Color (Box 200)
    - Urban Gardening Program, 1988-1990; cuid1223; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program, 1990-1999; cuid1224; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - A Mid Summer's Day Fair, 1989/06/23; cuid1225; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Advisory Committee, 1995-2001; cuid1226; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Anniversary, 20th, 1997; cuid1227; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Fact Sheet, cuid1228; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Friend of 4-H certificate, cuid1229; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Guidelines, 1988/11; cuid1230; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - History, cuid1231; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Impact Statement, 1998; cuid1232; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Media Hits, cuid1233; 1 Items (Box 200)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Special Events, 1987-1992; cuid1234; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Summary, 1985-1987; cuid1235; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Surveys and Evaluations, cuid1236; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Ten Years, 1988; cuid1237; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Working with Youth in Garden Projects, cuid1238; 1 Items (Box 200)
    - Urban Gardening Program - Workshops, Winter, 1986-1995; cuid1239; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Program (English version), undated; cuid1240; 1 Items; Audio--Tape--101/2" Reel
    - Urban Gardening Program (Spanish version), undated; cuid1241; 1 Items; Audio--Tape--101/2" Reel
    - Urban Gardening Quarterly, 1990-1998; cuid1242; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Quarterly, 1996-1998; cuid1243; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Quarterly, Winter, 1997; cuid1244; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Urban Gardening Tour, 1986-1990; cuid1245; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Watermelons - Farmers' Bulletin #1394, 1951/02; cuid1246; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - What Good is Community Greening?, 199506; cuid1247; 1 Items (Box 200)
    - Your City Garden Guide, 1979; cuid1248; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Youth Entrepreneur Symposium, 1999/04/07; cuid1249; 1 Items (Box 199)
    - Philadelphia Housing, 2000-2005 (Box 239)
  - Pike County
    - Agent Reports, 1924-1975; cuid1274; 1 Items (Box 80)
    - Agent Reports, 1976-1988; cuid1276; 1 Items (Box 81)
    - Annual Report, 1924-1969; cuid1280 (Box 197)
    - Annual Report, 1988; cuid1277 (Box 197)
    - Annual Report, 1991; cuid1278; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1996; cuid1279; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1997-2003; cuid1281 (Box 197)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 278)
  - Potter County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1950; cuid1282; 1 Items (Box 81)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1983; cuid1283; 1 Items (Box 82)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1916-1966; cuid1285; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1988; cuid1286; 1 Items (Box 173)
  - Schuylkill County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1960; cuid1287; 1 Items (Box 83)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1983; cuid1288; 1 Items (Box 84)
    - Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2006-2007 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2011 (Box 278)
  - Snyder County
    - Agent Reports, 1920-1935; cuid1289; 1 Items (Box 84)
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1968; cuid1290; 1 Items (Box 85)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1985; cuid1291; 1 Items (Box 85)
    - Agent Reports, 1968-1978; cuid1292; 1 Items (Box 104)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1985; cuid1293; 1 Items (Box 85)
  - Somerset County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1935; cuid1294; 1 Items (Box 85)
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1985; cuid1295; 1 Items (Box 86)
    - Agent Reports, 1967-1985; cuid1296; 1 Items (Box 86)
    - Anniversary, Golden, 1915-1965; cuid1297; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2003 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 278)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid1298; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Five Year Plan of Work, 1979-1984; cuid1299; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Southeast Region
    - Accomplishment Report, 2005-2006 (Box 278)
    - Strategic Plan, 2004 (Box 278)
    - Strategic Plan, 2004-2009 (Box 277)
  - Southwest Region, Harrisburg
    - Affirmative Action/Civil Rights Annual Report, 1994-1995; cuid1300; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Newsletter, 2002 (Box 277)
    - Newsletter, 2004 (Box 278)
    - Strategic Plan, 2005-2008 (Box 278)
  - Sullivan County
    - Agent Reports, 1918-1969; cuid1301; 1 Items (Box 87)
    - Agent Reports, 1970-1983; cuid1303; 1 Items (Box 88)
    - Agent Reports, 1985; cuid1305; 1 Items (Box 88)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 277)
  - Susquehanna County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1940; cuid1306; 1 Items (Box 88)
    - Agent Reports, 1941-1976; cuid1307; 1 Items (Box 89)
    - Agent Reports, 1977-1983; cuid1308; 1 Items (Box 90)
    - Agent Reports, 1985; cuid1309; 1 Items (Box 90)
    - Anniversary, 50th and 75th, 1916-1991; cuid1310; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid1311; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2003 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 278)
    - Highlights, 2000 (Box 277)
  - Temple County
    - Agent Reports, 1982-1983; cuid1312; 1 Items (Box 103)
  - Tioga County
    - Ag Banquet, 26th Annual, 2007 (Box 278)
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1950; cuid1313; 1 Items (Box 90)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1983; cuid1314; 1 Items (Box 91)
    - Agent Reports, 1985; cuid1315; 1 Items (Box 91)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid1316; 1 Items (Box 173)
  - Union County
    - Affirmative Action, 2008 (Box 268)
    - Agent Reports, 1919-1960; cuid1317; 1 Items (Box 92)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1967; cuid1318; 1 Items (Box 93)
    - Agent Reports, 1968-1978; cuid1320; 1 Items (Box 104)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1985; cuid1321; 1 Items (Box 93)
    - Agricultural Sciences College Directory, 1993-1994 (Box 272)
    - Agronomy, 2010-2011 (Box 275)
    - Agronomy newspaper clippings, 2004-2007 (Box 272)
    - Agronomy newspaper clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 273)
    - Annual Desk Audit, 2004-2005 (Box 272)
    - Annual Desk Audit, 2006-2007 (Box 267)
    - Annual Desk Audit, 2007 (Box 265)
    - Annual Desk Audit, 2007-2010 (Box 266)
    - Annual Desk Audit, 2010-2012 (Box 266)
    - Annual Desk Audit, 2014 (Box 267)
    - Annual Desk Audit and meeting minutes, 2003-2005 (Box 274)
    - Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 274)
    - Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 274)
    - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 272)
    - Annual Meeting, 2006 (Box 274)
    - Annual Meeting, 2008 (Box 270)
    - Annual Meeting Information, 1999 (Box 270)
    - Annual Report, 1938 (Box 272)
    - Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 270)
    - Annual Report, 2008-2009 (Box 272)
    - Annual Report Committee, 1997 (Box 270)
    - Autism Proposal, 2007 (Box 271)
    - Better Kid Care, 1999-2000 (Box 271)
    - Better Kid Care, 2002-2003 (Box 271)
    - BUILD, 2006 (Box 271)
    - Business Directory, 2005 (Box 274)
    - Business Partners, 2005 (Box 271)
    - Capital Days, 2008 (Box 264)
    - CASPAR, 2005 (Box 270)
    - Caucus Trustees, 2009 (Box 272)
    - CCRD, 2006-2007 (Box 271)
    - CCRD, 2007-2008 (Box 271)
    - CCRD Grant, 2005 (Box 267)
    - CCRD newspaper articles, 2005 (Box 266)
    - Census Information, 2000 (Box 267)
    - Childcare Listings, 2009 (Box 274)
    - Child Care newspaper clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 273)
    - Child Care newspaper clippings, 2010-2011 (Box 267)
    - Child Care Providers Directory, 2003 (Box 265)
    - Civil Rights Act, 1964 (Box 275)
    - Civil Rights Review, 1990-1994 (Box 265)
    - Civil Rights Review information, 2007 (Box 267)
    - Clover News, 2008 (Box 270)
    - Club Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 270)
    - Community Engagement Program, 2004-2005 (Box 265)
    - Community Engagement Report, 2005 (Box 265)
    - Community Engagement Team Meetings, 2006-2008 (Box 271)
    - Community Planning for Early Care, 2004 (Box 265)
    - Community Planning for Early Care and Education, 2003-2004 (Box 265)
    - Community Planning for Early Childcare, 2003-2004 (Box 265)
    - Community Planning for Early Childcare articles, 2005 (Box 265)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, and general information, 2005-2006 (Box 272)
    - Cooperative Extension - 75 years Young (photographs and captions), undated (Box 272)
    - Cooperative Extension Highlights, 1998 (Box 272)
    - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 272)
    - Correspondence, 2011 (Box 272)
    - Correspondence and Information, 2010 (Box 275)
    - County Extension Board, 2009 (Box 271)
    - CRA Review, 1995 (Box 270)
    - Dairy, 2008 (Box 268)
    - Dairy, 2009 (Box 271)
    - Dairy, 2010 (Box 269)
    - Dairy Newsletter, 2009 (Box 264)
    - Dairy newspaper clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 273)
    - Delegate Election of Trustees, 1998-2002 (Box 272)
    - District V - Horse Show, 2008-2009 (Box 264)
    - Early Childcare and Education, 2007-2008 (Box 271)
    - Early Care and Education Engagement Team Meeting, 2006-2007 (Box 265)
    - Early Care and Education Task Force, 2004 (Box 265)
    - Early Child Care Newsletter, 2007 (Box 265)
    - Events, meeting calendar, 1998-2004 (Box 274)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1974-1977 (Box 266)
    - Extension Annual Report, 2010 (Box 269)
    - Extension Board, 2007-2008 (Box 271)
    - Extension Board, 2009-2011 (Box 269)
    - Family Living Advisory Group, 2006 (Box 267)
    - Family Living newspaper articles, 2004-2005 (Box 265)
    - Family Living newspaper clippings, 2005-2007 (Box 273)
    - Farm Tours photographs, 1940-1950 (Box 273)
    - Field Notebook, 1987-2011 (Box 275)
    - Food Safety magnets, undated (Box 275)
    - 4-H, 2009 (Box 270)
    - 4-H Advisory Board, 2007-2008 (Box 268)
    - 4-H Advisory Board, 2009 (Box 270)
    - 4-H Advisory Board, 2010-2011 (Box 269)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee, 1990-1997 (Box 270)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee, 2001-2008 (Box 270)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 274)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 271)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee, 2010 (Box 271)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee, 2012-2014 (Box 274)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee Meeting, 2006 (Box 265)
    - 4-H Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 2009 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Ambassador Program, 1994-1997 (Box 270)
    - 4-H Awards, 2008 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Camp packets, 2008 (Box 275)
    - 4-H Club Lists, 1992-1997 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Club Lists, 2000-2006 (Box 264)
    - 4-H County Ambassador, 2009 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Meetings, 2008 (Box 265)
    - 4-H Member List, 2007-2008 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Members and Leaders, 2008 (Box 271)
    - 4-H newspaper clippings, 2005-2007 (Box 272)
    - 4-H newspaper clippings, 2007-2009 (Box 268)
    - 4-H newspaper clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 273)
    - 4-H newspaper clippings, 2011-2012 (Box 267)
    - 4-H Officers and Training Books, undated (Box 269)
    - 4-H pamphlets, clippings and reports, 2014-2015 (Box 272)
    - 4-H Photographs, 1930-1950 (Box 274)
    - 4-H Photographs, 1930-1970 (Box 275)
    - 4-H Photographs, 1930-1990 (Box 273)
    - 4-H Photographs, 1936-1938 (Box 271)
    - 4-H Photographs, 1938-1940 (Box 269)
    - 4-H Photographs, 1946-1994 (Box 269)
    - 4-H Photographs, 1950-1960 (Box 271)
    - 4-H Programs, 2011 (Box 275)
    - 4-H Programs, Sun Area, 2008 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Project Completions, 1997-2006 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Recognition, 2009 (Box 270)
    - 4-H recognition, 2011 (Box 267)
    - 4-H Recognition Award Meeting, 2008-2009 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Recognition Event, 2006 (Box 274)
    - 4-H Recognition Event, 2009 (Box 272)
    - 4-H Reports, 2009 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Roundup, 2008 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Roundup, 2009 (Box 265)
    - 4-H Scholarships, 1998-2002 (Box 264)
    - 4-H slides, undated (Box 274)
    - 4-H Volunteer Recognition Dinner, 2008-2009 (Box 264)
    - 4-H Volunteer Survey, 2008 (Box 264)
    - Fund Drive, 2008-2009 (Box 264)
    - Goals Table, 2005 (Box 265)
    - Grant Applications, 2006-2007 (Box 271)
    - Guidelines for Advisory and Planning Committees, 2007 (Box 268)
    - Home and Gardener School, 2009-2012 (Box 269)
    - Home Gardeners School, 2005 (Box 272)
    - Home Garden School, 2007-2008 (Box 268)
    - Home Gardeners School Committee, 2005 (Box 268)
    - Horse and Pony Roundup, 2008 (Box 265)
    - Horse and Pony Roundup, 2009 (Box 264)
    - Lady Lions Day, 2008 (Box 265)
    - Leadership Ideas, 1983 (Box 265)
    - Livestock Dairy Meeting, 2008 (Box 265)
    - Livestock Knowledge Night, 2008 (Box 265)
    - Livestock Newsletter, 2009 (Box 265)
    - Master Gardener, 2007 (Box 267)
    - Master Gardener, 2010-2011 (Box 267)
    - Master Gardeners clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 275)
    - Master Gardener newspaper clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 273)
    - Master Gardeners newspaper clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 268)
    - Master Gardeners newspaper clippings, 2008-2010 (Box 271)
    - Master Gardeners newspaper clippings, 2009 (Box 272)
    - Master Gardeners newspaper clippings, 2009 (Box 274)
    - Master Gardeners newspaper clippings, 2010-2011 (Box 267)
    - Master Gardener Program, 2011 (Box 272)
    - Meeting Agenda and Notes, 2008 (Box 264)
    - Meeting Minutes, 2006-2009 (Box 272)
    - Meeting Minutes and Financial Reports, 2006 (Box 274)
    - Meeting Minutes and Information, 2011-2012 (Box 267)
    - Newspaper articles, 2009-2010 (Box 266)
    - Newspaper articles, 2012 (Box 266)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2002 (Box 274)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2004 (Box 274)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2005-2006 (Box 271)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2006-2008 (Box 268)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2012 (Box 267)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2014-2015 (Box 272)
    - Newspaper clippings and information, 2005 (Box 271)
    - Newspaper clippings and information, 2005-2006 (Box 268)
    - Newspaper clippings and information, 2007 (Box 267)
    - NRA Grant Information, 2008 (Box 265)
    - Penn State Satellite Network, 2008 (Box 272)
    - Pennsylvania Farm Show, 2007-2008 (Box 265)
    - Professional Development, 2007-2008 (Box 265)
    - Proposals, 2006-2007 (Box 271)
    - Public Notifications, 2007 (Box 275)
    - Publicity Notebook, 2005-2008 (Box 275)
    - Relocation Guide, 2008 (Box 275)
    - Satellite Equipment, 1995 (Box 272)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 2007 (Box 268)
    - Staff Meetings, 2008-2010 (Box 271)
    - State Achievement Days, 2005-2008 (Box 264)
    - Steering Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 271)
    - TAC Meeting, 2009 (Box 264)
    - Teen Advisory Committee, 2008 (Box 264)
    - Teen Ambassador, 2009 (Box 264)
    - Teen Council, 2009 (Box 264)
    - Teen Day, 2006-2009 (Box 264)
    - Toddler Topics, 2002-2005 (Box 266)
    - Travel Information including maps, undated (Box 275)
    - Trustee Caucus, 2008 (Box 272)
    - Trustee Meeting, 2002-2008 (Box 272)
    - Turf and Ornamentals Meeting, 2010 (Box 271)
    - Union County Libraries Listing, 2005 (Box 274)
    - Union County Today, 2007 (Box 275)
    - West End Fair, 2005 (Box 272)
    - West End Fair - 80th Annual, 2005 (Box 273)
    - West End Fair - 81st Annual, 2006 (Box 273)
    - West End Fair, 2007-2009 (Box 264)
    - West End Fair, 2007-2011 (Box 270)
    - West End Fair, 2008-2009 (Box 271)
    - West End Fair - 84th Annual, 2008-2009 (Box 275)
    - West End Fair, 2008-2010 (Box 274)
    - West End Fair - 90th Annual, 2015 (Box 273)
    - West End Fair newspaper clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 273)
    - West Nile Virus Grant, 2011 (Box 272)
    - Woman's Recreational Leadership Camp, July 1938 (Box 272)
    - Woman's Recreational Leadership Camp, July 1940 (Box 272)
  - Venango County
    - Agent Reports, 1916-1960; cuid1322; 1 Items (Box 93)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1917-1967; cuid1323; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1980-1982; cuid1324; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid1325; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2005-2006 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2009-2010 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 90th Anniversary, 2005 (Box 277)
    - Agent Reports, 1961-1981 (Box 94)
  - Warren County
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1981; cuid1326; 1 Items (Box 95)
    - Agents Dues Paid - Listing Book with photographs, undated; cuid1328; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 169)
    - Alpha Omicron Chapter - Constitution and Bylaws, 1995; cuid1329 (Box 169)
    - Alpha Omicron Chapter - Finance Committee Report, 1995; cuid1330 (Box 169)
    - Alpha Omicron Chapter - Treasurer's Report, 1994-1995; cuid1331 (Box 169)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1915-1965; cuid1332; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Anniversary, 75th, 1915-1990; cuid1333; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1970; cuid1334; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 1974; cuid1335; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1977-1987; cuid1337; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid1338; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 1992-1993; cuid1336; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Assets Listing, 1987-1990; cuid1339 (Box 169)
    - Cooperative Extension - Extension Retirees Listing, 1995/03; cuid1340 (Box 169)
    - Cooperative Extension - Pennsylvania Tradition flyer, undated; cuid1341 (Box 169)
    - Correspondence, 1995; cuid1342 (Box 169)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1992; cuid1343 (Box 169)
    - County Extension Directors Summary, undated; cuid1344 (Box 169)
    - Court House Dedication, 1963/04/20; cuid1345; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Extension Extended Newsletter, 1995/03; cuid1346 (Box 169)
    - Extension Extended Newsletter, 1996/03; cuid1347 (Box 169)
    - Extension Retirees Party, 1999/09/17; cuid1348; Photographic--Slides--35mm (Box 180)
    - Extension Service, undated; cuid1349; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Meeting Minutes and Records, 1980-1988; cuid1350 (Box 180)
    - NACAA 70th Annual Meeting booklet, 1985; cuid1351 (Box 180)
    - NACAA Annual Meeting booklet, 1997; cuid1352 (Box 180)
    - NACAA Annual Meetings, 1983-1986; cuid1353 (Box 180)
    - NACAA Annual Meetings Accounts, 1985; cuid1354 (Box 180)
    - NACAA Annual Report, 1985; cuid1355 (Box 169)
    - NACAA County Agent, 1980; cuid1356 (Box 169)
    - NACAA County Agent, 1999; cuid1357 (Box 180)
    - NACAA Meeting Committee Progress Report, 1985; cuid1358 (Box 169)
    - NACAA National Officers Signs, undated; cuid1359 (Box 169)
    - NACAA State Chairs correspondence, 1995; cuid1360 (Box 169)
    - National Association County Agricultural Agents correspondence, 1995; cuid1361 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - 4H Committee, 1995-1998; cuid1362 (Box 180)
    - PACAA - Annual Report, 1994; cuid1363 (Box 180)
    - PACAA - Annual Report, 1998; cuid1364 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Annual Report, 1998; cuid1365 (Box 180)
    - PACAA - Annual Reports, 1973; cuid1366 (Box 180)
    - PACAA - Annual Reports, 1964-1971; cuid1367 (Box 180)
    - PACAA - Annual Reports, 1975-1979; cuid1368 (Box 180)
    - PACAA - Annual Reports, 1980-1993; cuid1369 (Box 180)
    - PACAA - Annual Reports, 1986-1994; cuid1370 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Awards Luncheon, 1998/11/17; cuid1371 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Committee Assignments, 1995; cuid1372 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Committee Assignments, 1991-1992; cuid1373 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Correspondence and Notes, 1995; cuid1374 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - County Agents Retirement Committee, 1954-1984; cuid1375 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Investment, 1987-1989; cuid1376 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Investment Account, 1995; cuid1377 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Life Membership Committee, 1988-1993; cuid1378 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Meeting Minutes, 1995/05/16; cuid1379 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Meeting Minutes, 1941-1971; cuid1380 (Box 180)
    - PACAA - Member's Handbook, 1989-1992; cuid1381 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Membership and Board Meeting Minutes, 1982-1983; cuid1382 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Meritorious Service Certificate (samples), undated; cuid1383 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Off Cuff newsletter, 1991/06; cuid1384 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - President Elect Officer's Handbook, 1987; cuid1385 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Retirees Committee - Officer's Handbook, 1987; cuid1386 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Retirees Spring Get-Together, 1995; cuid1387 (Box 169)
    - PACAA - Washington County Agricultural Fair, Inc. - Certificate of Appreciation, 1985; cuid1388 (Box 169)
    - PACAA (Pennsylvania Association of Country Agriculture Agents) - Off Cuff newsletter, 1995/02/17; cuid1389 (Box 169)
    - Pest Alert, 1985; cuid1390 (Box 169)
    - Photographs, undated; cuid1391; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 169)
    - Program Highlights, 1996; cuid1392; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Program Highlights, 1999 (Box 277)
    - Reminiscence for Bernie Wingert, 1984/02/25; cuid1393; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Agent Reports, 1915-1935 (Box 94)
  - Washington County
    - Activities Report, 1912-1962; cuid1394 (Box 182)
    - Adult Education Home Economics newspaper clippings, 1969; cuid1395 (Box 182)
    - Adult Health Education, 1957; cuid1396 (Box 182)
    - Adult Home Economics newspaper clippings, 1963-1964; cuid1397 (Box 182)
    - Agent Reports, 1912-1969; cuid1398; 1 Items (Box 96)
    - Agent Reports, 1970-1976; cuid1400; 1 Items (Box 97)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1980; cuid1401; 1 Items (Box 97)
    - Agriculture Bureau Meeting Minutes, 1916-1960; cuid1402; 1 Items (Box 167)
    - Agriculture Development in Pittsburgh District - Progress Report, 1949/04; cuid1403 (Box 182)
    - Anniversary, 50th newspaper clippings, 1962/09/12; cuid1404 (Box 182)
    - Anniversary, Golden Harvest, 1912-1962; cuid1405; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual County Agent Reports, 1917-1961; cuid1406; 45 Items (Box 167)
    - Annual Report, 1976; cuid1407; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid1409; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2005 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2011 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report/Calendar of Events, 2000-2001 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report and Calendar of Events, 1996-1997; cuid1408; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Statistical Report, 1962; cuid1410; 1 Items (Box 167)
    - Boys 4-H Clubs, 1921-1936; cuid1411 (Box 182)
    - Census Bulletin, 1920-1940; cuid1412 (Box 182)
    - Constitution and Meeting Minutes, 1912-1916; cuid1413; 1 Items (Box 167)
    - Correspondence, 1937-1948; cuid1414 (Box 182)
    - County-Wide Dairy Day program, 1968/09/19; cuid1415 (Box 182)
    - Dairy Day newspaper clippings, 1965; cuid1416 (Box 182)
    - Economic Handbook, 1930; cuid1417 (Box 182)